A Guide to the Records of the Drug Policy Office of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1987-1994 (bulk 1990-1994)
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Grants, 1987-1994., Extent: 25.90 cu. ft. (74 boxes) (Box 22-94)
  Organizations eligible to apply for the grants included parent groups, community action agencies, community-based organizations, and other public entities and private nonprofit entities. Community service boards, police departments, mental health agencies, and educational institutions ranging from elementary and high schools to colleges and universities applied for grants. Several programs were specifically aimed at educating students such as Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, DARE, Student Assistance Programs (SAP), Police, Public Educators, Peer Facilitators, Utilizing their leadership for students at risk (PULSAR), and Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault on Campuses (SASA). Activities funded by the grants include programs for alcohol and other drug abuse prevention, early intervention, rehabilitation and education; training programs for teachers, counselors, parents, local law enforcement officials, judicial officials, and community leaders; the development and distribution of educational and informational materials; technical assistance to help community based organizations and educational agencies in the planning and implementation of drug abuse prevention; activities to encourage the coordination of alcohol and other abuse education and prevention programs with related community efforts and resources; drug abuse education and prevention centers for providing outreach, consultation, training, and referral services to schools, organizations, and community members; and activities that promote, establish, and maintain drug-free school zones for schools.
  The grants are organized by either a grouping of similar grants or by the name of the organization overseeing the grants. Larger grouping of similar grants include grants for Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week; Bill of Rights for Drug Independence; Children of Alcoholics (COA); Emergency Grants to localities; Rural Grants; Student Assistance Programs (SAP); Intensified Drug Enforcement Assistance (IDEA); Police, Public Educators, Peer Facilitators, Utilizing their leadership for students at risk (PULSAR); Community Against Drug Related Activities (CADRA); Drug Abuse Resistance Education (DARE); Safe Neighborhoods; Higher Education Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault on Campuses (SASA); and Commonwealth Alliance for Drug Rehabilitation and Education (CADRE).
  Individual grants, arranged by the organization overseeing the grants, include programs such as: Peer Outreach Program (POP); Substance abuse prevention for childbearing youth; Chemical Abuse Prevention through Educational Services (CAPES); Positive Images lead to Positive Actions (PIPA); Preventing Adolescent Pregnancy (PAP); Helping Parents and Youth Talk; Teen Mentor programs; At Risk Student Support Groups; School Success for At-Risk Students; Safe Neighborhoods; The Word is No (TWIN); Students participating in a creative environment (SPACE); Youth Outreach; Project Insight for Youth; Project Mission (Middle School Substance Intervention); Project Transition; Court Appointed Special Advocate Program for High Risk Youth (CASA); Latchkey Child Enrichment Program; Prevention through Recreation Individual Instruction and Drug Education (PRIDE); Youth Against Drugs (YAD); New Horizons for Substance Abuse Prevention: Engaging High Risk Youth; Project Link (Perinatal addiction); Project POSSE; 80 Proof Double Standard; Project Life Line; Project DAWN (Developing a Wider and Wiser Network); and many others.
  Along with a copy of the official grant many organizations also included detailed proposals with brochures, project plans, background information, future plans, resumes, letters of support, and progress reports. Of note are the Performance Reports submitted to the Office of the Governor, 1989-1993. The Performance Reports, 1989-1992, are organized numerically by some type of unidentifiable internal numbering system. The Performance Reports, 1992-1993, are organized alphabetically by organizational name. The Performance Reports forms were required by the Office of the Governor and include information on number of people served; demographic information; types of services provided; narrative of the project; and assessments of the projects effectiveness. Some Performance Reports were also interspersed within the individual grant folders.
  Also included are the grant files from the previous administration when Attorney General Mary Sue Terry chaired the Governor's Council on Drug and Abuse Problems. In 1986 the combined offices of the Attorney General, the Department of Education, the Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, and the Department of Social Services created the Commonwealth's first coordinated interagency effort to decrease youth alcohol and other drug abuse. The plan was named CADRE, the Commonwealth Alliance for Drug Rehabilitation and Education. Dr. John Slattery of the Department of Social Services at Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU) was the grants administrator. Included are copies of numerous CADRE and other High Risk Youth grants awarded during this time.
  - Adapts, Inc., 1987-1990 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Albemarle County Public Schools, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Abingdon High School, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Brentsville Middle-Senior High School (Nokesville, Va.), 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, William Byrd High School (Vinton, Va.), 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Cave Springs High School (Roanoke, Va.), 1993 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Clarke County Public Schools, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Craddock High School (Portsmouth, Va.), 1992 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, E.B. Stanley Middle School (Abingdon, Va.), 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Franklin City Public Schools, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Gar-Field Senior High School (Woodbridge, Va.), 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Glenver High School (Salem, Va.), 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Halifax County Junior High School, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Jefferson Forest High School (Forest, Va.), 1993 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, John F. Kennedy High School (Richmond, Va.), 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Liberty High School (Bedford, Va.), 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Marion Senior High School (Marion, Va.), 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Martinsville High School, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Jefferson Forest High School (Forest, Va.), Scrapbook, 1993 (Box 23)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Menchville High School (Newport News, Va.), 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Metz Junior High School (Manassas, Va.), 1993 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, George H. Moody Middle School (Richmond, Va.), 1993 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Narrows High School (Narrows, Va.), 1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Northwood Middle School (Broadford, Va.), 1993 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Norview High School (Norfolk, Va.), 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Paul VI High School (Fairfax, Va.), 1993 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Roanoke County Career Center, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Western Branch High School (Chesapeake, Va.), 1992 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Alexandria City Public Schools, 1989-1991 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Amherst County, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Arlington, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Bill of Rights, Bedford Middle School-Pennington Middle School, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Charlotte County Public Schools, 1988-1990 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Chesapeake Bay Youth Conservation Corps, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Children of Alcoholics (COA), Bristol Public Schools, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Children of Alcoholics, Colonial Community Services Board (Williamsburg, Va.), 1992 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Children of Alcoholics, Dept. Mental Health Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Children of Alcoholics, Dickenson County Community Services Board, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Children of Alcoholics, Franklin County Public Schools, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Children of Alcoholics, Hampton-Newport News Community Services Board, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Children of Alcoholics, Loudoun County Mental Health Services, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Children of Alcoholics, Middle Peninsula-Northern Neck Community Services Board, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Children of Alcoholics, Prince Edward County Public Schools, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Children of Alcoholics, Richmond Area Community Services Board, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Children of Alcoholics, Rockbridge Area Community Services Board, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - C.L.E.A.N., Inc. (Clarke and Frederick Counties and Winchester, Va.), 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 7-8)
  - C.L.E.A.N., Inc., 1990-1993 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Colonial Coast Girl Scouts Council (Newport News and Norfolk, Va.), 1989-1991 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - CADRA (Community Against Drug Related Activities), Norfolk, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - CADRA, Norfolk, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - CADRA, Norfolk, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - CADRE (Commonwealth Alliance for Drug Rehabilitation and Education), Accomack County, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - CADRE, Alleghany Highlands, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - CADRE, Buckingham County, 1988-1990 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - CADRE, Buckingham County, 1989-1991 (Box 26, Folder 6-7)
  - CADRE, Chesterfield County, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - CADRE, Coalfield County, 1989-1992 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - CADRE, Craig County, 1988-1992 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - CADRE, Danville, 1989-1991 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - CADRE, Eastern Shore, 1989-1991 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - CADRE, Essex County, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - CADRE, Greene County, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - CADRE, Hampton City, 1989-1991 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - CADRE, Hanover County, 1989-1991 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - CADRE, Mathews County, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - CADRE, New Kent County, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - CADRE, Norfolk, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - CADRE, Prince William County, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - CADRE, Staunton, 1988-1990 (Box 28, Folder 5-6)
  - CADRE, Tazewell County, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - CADRE, Tri-Cities Area (Colonial Heights, Hopewell, and Petersburg, Va.), 1988-1990 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - CADRE, Tri-Cities Area, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - CADRE, Virginia Beach, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - CADRE, Washington County, 1988-1990 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - CADRE, Wise County, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - CADRE, Wise County, 1989-1991 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - CADRE, State, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - CADRE, State, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - CADRE, Governor's Alliance Line, 1989-1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - CADRE, Governor's Alliance Line, 1991-1993 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - CADRE, Governor's Alliance Newsletters, 1991-1993 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - CADRE, Video production, 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - CADRE, Workshops, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Connections (Catholic Charities of Richmond), 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Connections (Catholic Charities of Richmond), 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Connections (Catholic Charities of Richmond), 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Council on Child Day Care and Early Childhood Programs, 1991-1993 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Craig County, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Cumberland Plateau Regional Housing Authority, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Danville-Pittsylvania Mental Health Services Board, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Danville-Pittsylvania Mental Health Services Board, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Daily Planet and Virginia Coalition for the Homeless, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Department for the Aging, Aging and Substance Abuse COmmunity Resources Directory, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Department for the Aging, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Department for the Aging, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Department for the Aging, Brochures, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 4-5)
  - Department for the Aging, Video training, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Department of ABC (Alcohol Beverage Control), 1989-1991 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Department of ABC (Alcohol Beverage Control), 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Department of ABC (Alcohol Beverage Control), Pamphlets, 1991-1993 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Department of Education, First Annual Statewide School/Community Student Assistance Conference, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Department of Education, Parent Education Training of Trainers, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Department of Education, Youth Risk Behaviors Study, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, 1988-1992 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Council on Coordinating Prevention Program Development, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Department of Personnel and Training, 1990-1992 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Department of Social Services, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Department of Youth and Family Services, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Department of Youth and Family Services, Local Network Coordinator, 1991-1993 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Department of Youth and Family Services, Substance Abuse Managers, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Department of Youth and Family Services, Substance Abuse Programs, 1990-1992 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - DARE (Drug Abuse Resistance Education), General, Application package (blank example), 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - DARE, General, Application package (blank example), 1992 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - DARE, General, Application package (blank example), 1993 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - DARE, General, Coordinator positions, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - DARE, General, Training seminar, 1991 July 29-August 9 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - DARE, Accomack County, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - DARE, Albemarle County, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - DARE, Albemarle County, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - DARE, Appomattox County, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - DARE, Ashland, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - DARE, Bath County, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - DARE, Bedford County, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - DARE, Bristol, 1991-1993 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - DARE, Brunswick County, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - DARE, Buena Vista, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - DARE, Campbell County, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - DARE, Charles City County, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - DARE, Chesapeake, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - DARE, Chesterfield County, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - DARE, Christiansburg, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - DARE, Clarke County, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - DARE, Culpeper County, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - DARE, Culpeper County, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - DARE, Fairfax County, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - DARE, Franklin County, 1991-1993 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - DARE, Frederick County, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - DARE, Galax, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - DARE, Greene County, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - DARE, Greensville County, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - DARE, Halifax County, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - DARE, Hanover County, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - DARE, Highland County, 1991-1993 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - DARE, Hopewell, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - DARE, Lancaster County, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - DARE, Leesburg, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - DARE, Lunenburg County, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 3-4)
  - DARE, Lunenburg County, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - DARE, Lunenburg County, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - DARE, Manassas, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - DARE, Manassas, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - DARE, Marion, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - DARE, Mathews County, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - DARE, Middlesex County, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - DARE, Nelson County, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - DARE, Newport News, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - DARE, Newport News, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - DARE, Newport News, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 1-4)
  - DARE, Norfolk, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - DARE, Norton, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - DARE, Orange County, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - DARE, Page County, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - DARE, Page County, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - DARE, Petersburg, 1991-1993 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - DARE, Poquoson, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - DARE, Powhatan County, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - DARE, Prince Edward County, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - DARE, Prince George County, 1991-1993 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - DARE, Prince William County, 1991-1993 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - DARE, Pulaski County, 1991-1993 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - DARE, Rappahannock County, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - DARE, Roanoke City, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - DARE, Roanoke County, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - DARE, Salem, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - DARE, Scott County, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - DARE, Smyth County, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - DARE, Spotsylvania County, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - DARE, Stafford County, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 3-4)
  - DARE, Staunton, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - DARE, Suffolk, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - DARE, Tazewell County, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - DARE, Tazewell County, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - DARE, Vienna, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - DARE, Virginia Beach, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - DARE, Warren County, 1991-1993 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - DARE, Washington County, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - DARE, Williamsburg-James City County, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - DARE, Winchester, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - DARE, Wise County, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - DARE, Wythe County, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - DARE, Wytheville, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - DARE, York County, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - DARE, York County, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - DARE, Department of Education, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - DARE, Department of State Police, 1988-1990 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - DARE, Department of State Police, 1991-1993 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Eastern Shore Community Service Board, 1987-1990 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Shore Rural Health System, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Shore Rural Health System, 1989-1990 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Eastern Shore Rural Health System, 1989-1990 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Educational and Training Communications, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Emergency Grants to Schools, Alexandria Public Schools, 1989-1991 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Emergency Grants to Schools, Alexandria Public Schools, 1991-1993 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Emergency Grants to Schools, Danville Public Schools, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
  - Emergency Grants to Schools, Dept. of Correctional Education, 1990-1992 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Emergency Grants to Schools, Norfolk Public Schools, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Emergency Grants to Schools, Petersburg Public Schools, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Emergency Grants to Schools, Portsmouth Public Schools, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Emergency Grants to Schools, Richmond Public Schools, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Fairfax County YMCA, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Family Services of Norfolk, 1988-1989 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Family Services of Norfolk, 1989-1991 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Family Services of Tidewater, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Fairfax County Public Schools, 1987-1989 (Box 44, Folder 3-4)
  - Five Rivers Regional Educational Service (West Point, Va.), 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - FOCUS Women's Resource Center (Charlottesville, Va.), 1991 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Girls, Inc., of Tidewater (Virginia Beach, Va.), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - George Mason Junior-Senior High School (Falls Church, Va.), 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - George Mason University, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - George Mason University, 1989-1992 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Girls, Inc. of Tidewater (Virginia Beach, Va.), 1992 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Alliance for A Drug-Free Virginia, 1991-1992 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Alliance for A Drug-Free Virginia, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - GRIP (Greater Richmond Informed Parents), 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 6-7)
  - Halifax County Public Schools, 1989-1990 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Hampton (Alternatives School), 1988-1989 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Hampton Police Division, 1989-1992 (Box 46, Folder 3-5)
  - Hampton Police Division, 1990-1992 (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
  - Hampton University, 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Hanover County Community Service Board, 1988-1991 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Harrisonburg-Rockingham Community Service Board, 1987-1989 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Harrisonburg-Rockingham Community Service Board, 1987-1989 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Henrico County, Essex Village, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Henrico County Public Schools, 1989-1991 (Box 48, Folder 3-4)
  - Henrico Area Mental Health Mental Retardation Services, 1989-1991 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Hopkins House Association, Inc. (Alexandria, Va.), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - IDEA (Intensified Drug Enforcement Assistance), Alexandria, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - IDEA, Arlington County, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - IDEA, Arlington County, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - IDEA, Ashland, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - IDEA, Bedford city, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - IDEA, Bristol, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - IDEA, Essex County, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - IDEA, Franklin County, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - IDEA, Fredericksburg, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - IDEA, Fredericksburg, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - IDEA, Giles County, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - IDEA, Giles County, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - IDEA, Halifax and Mecklenburg County, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - IDEA, Hampton, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - IDEA, Hanover County, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - IDEA, Hanover County, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - IDEA, Henrico County, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - IDEA, James City County, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - IDEA, Lancaster County, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - IDEA, Lynchburg, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - IDEA, Manassas, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - IDEA, Martinsville, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - IDEA, Martinsville, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - IDEA, Newport News, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - IDEA, Newport News, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - IDEA, Norfolk, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - IDEA, Norfolk, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - IDEA, North Central Virginia Regional Narcotics Task Force, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - IDEA, Northwest Virginia Drug Task Force, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - IDEA, Norton, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - IDEA, Norton, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - IDEA, Petersburg, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 7)